NYSUT Teacher Education Conference Board Files 6174/009
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- TECB Meeting Photographs, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  Albany 9/24. Black and white photo of Dr. Edward Iwanicki, professor of education leadership at University of Connecticut, speaking at TECB fall meeting, with NYSUT vice president Antonia Cortese; contact sheet of other photos taken at meeting; invoice from William Wren Photography
- TECB Conference Letter, 1990-1992 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  Newsletters, vol. 9, no. 2, spring 1990, and vol. 12, no. 1, fall 1992; cover letter from TECB inviting teacher educators to conference, "Reimagining Teaching and Teacher Education," held January 8, 1993
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  Desk calendar of staff consultant James Kiepper
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- TECB-Monthly Calendar, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Boyer School Reform Article, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Clipping from New York Teacher, May 28, 1984
- TECB Newsletter, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Fall. Handwritten notes re TECB fall meeting; list of articles for newsletter; document from State Education Department requesting reaction to proposed certification requirements for teachers of adult and continuing education; announcement for COTE/TECB conference, "Dismantling the Barriers to Minorities
- TECB Report/Background/Position Papers, 1980-1990 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  TECB position papers, "Teaching as a Profession: Toward the Promotion and Support of Competence" and "The Effective Teacher"; proposal, Reimagining the System of Teacher Education in New York State"; document, "History and Background of the Teacher Education Conference Board"; handwritten notes
- TECB Newsletter Vol. 9, No. 2, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- TECB Newsletter Vol. 7, No. 3, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- TECB Newsletter Vol. 7, No. 2, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- TECB Newsletter Vol. 8, No. 4, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- TECB Newsletter Vol. 12, No. 1, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- TECB Newsletter Vol. 11, No. 1, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- TECB Correspondence, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  "New Directions in Teacher Education for the 1990s: A Report on the Statewide Conversation about the Agenda for Teacher Education in a Democracy to the Education Commission for the States," by State Education Department (SED); SED press releases; "Teacher Education and the Future: Remarks of Chancellor R. Carlos Carballada to the Teacher Education Conference Board, September 25, 1992"; letter of thanks to Chancellor for attending TECB meeting; NYSUT document re Effective Teaching Program; correspondence from State Education Department re teacher certification
- NY Teacher Publication, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  Contact sheet for photographs of meeting
- Jim Kiepper, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  Agenda for TECB annual meeting, May 8, 1992; handwritten notes re meeting; treasurer's reports, 1985-1992; budget, 1991-92; staff consultant's report (Kiepper's), 1990-91, May 8, 1992; minutes of March 6, 1992, meeting; newspaper clippings; spring 1992 TECB newsletter, vol. 11, no. 2
- TECB Expenses, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  Invoices and copies of checks for typesetting and other services, including James Kiepper's consulting fees for TECB, signed by NYSUT vice president Antonia Cortese; copy of NYSUT check to TECB for 1992-93 dues, for $4000, signed by NYSUT president and TECB vice president Tom Hobart
- TECB Newsletter Vol. 5, No. 2, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- TECB Newsletter Vol. 7, No. 1, 1986-1987 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- TECB Newsletter Vol. 6, No. 2, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- TECB Newsletter Vol. 15, No. 2, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- TECB Newsletter Vol. 15, No. 1, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- TECB Newsletter Vol. 10, No. 1, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Blue Ribbon Task Force, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  Charge for Commissioner's Task Force on Teacher Education and Certification in New York (draft), May 19, 1975; final document, November 14, 1975; suggested list of members; TECB position paper, "The Effective Teacher"; related documents; correspondence
- TECB Meeting Fordham University, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  3/6/92. Agenda and handwritten notes of meeting; attendance sheet; minutes of December 13, 1991, meeting; memos re future role of TECB; treasurer's report; executive summary of report by Holmes Group, "Tomorrow's Schools: Principles for the Design of Professional Development Schools"; letter to TECB from State Education Department, asking for nominations to the Teacher Education, Certification and Practice Board (TECAP), February
- TECB Meeting 5/3/96, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  TECB board meeting minutes of November 1, 1995; handwritten notes of May 4, 1996, meeting; treasurer's report, April 30, 1996; budget for school year 1995-96; State Education Department press release, "Regents Vote: Students Must Pass Regents Exam," April 24, 1996; paper, "Recent Research on the Need for Recertification: A Brief Summary
- TECB Meeting, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  Agenda for November 1, 1995, meeting; memo from TECB subcommittee re concerns within teacher education
- TECB Meeting-Syracuse 9/28/95, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  Agenda for meeting of September 18, 1995; minutes of May 5, 1995, meeting; notes form meeting with Regents Chancellor Hayden on September 18; list of questions for Hayden from NYSUT vice president Toni Cortese; treasurer's report, August 31, 1995; description and mission statement of the University of the State of New York and Board of Regents, and list of members and committees
- TECB Meeting 5/5/95, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  Minutes of board meeting, May 5, 1995; agenda for annual meeting, May 5, 1995; proposed calendar 1995-96; staff consultant report, 1994-95 (Kiepper), May 5, 1995; letter inviting Education Commissioner Sobol to TECB meeting, September 26, 1994; expense invoices
- TECB Meeting and Dinner 12/8-9/94, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  Invoices; handwritten notes
- TECB Meeting 5/6/94, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  Proposed agenda for annual meeting, May 6, 1994; proposed calendar, 1994-95; invoices
- TECB Invitational Conference 1/8/92, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  Announcement and agenda for TECB invitational conference, "Re-Imagining Teaching and Teacher Education," January 8, 1993; filled-in registration forms; memo to TECB Executive Committee from staff consultant Jim Kiepper, listing suggested topics for conference, November 22, 1992; lists of names
- TECB Meeting 5/24/93, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  Proposed agenda for annual meeting of May 24, 1993; budget, 1993-94; treasurer's report, May 1993
- TECB Meeting NYC 12/13/91, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  Treasurer's report, December 13, 1991
- TECB Meeting 9/28/93, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  Invoices
- TECB Meeting-Conference Room A 10/11/91, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  Agenda; minutes of Annual Meeting, May 15, 1991; treasurer's report, October 11, 1991; TECB 1991-92 membership list as of October 11; memo re tentative list of articles for fall newsletter; discussion items for the Board of Regents; proposed amendments to Regulations of the Commissioner
- TECB Meeting 3/8/91, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  Correspondence re invitational conference on restructuring schools, held March 8, 1991; proposed agenda for TECB winter meeting, December 14, 1990
- TECB Meeting 3/28/91, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  Regents action item, "A New Compact for Learning: Improving Public Elementary, Middle, and Secondary Education Results in the 1990s," March 1991; list of 1990-91 members of Teacher Education, Certification and Practice Board (State Education Department); 1991-92 Executive Budget Proposals by the Business Council of NYS, Inc.; State Education Department press releases; memo from Kiepper re planning for annual meeting
- TECB Meeting 11/29/90, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  Letters from NYSUT vice president Antonia Cortese to individuals advising them that they would be nominated to serve on TECB, inviting them to subsequent meeting on December 14
- TECB Meeting 5/15/91, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  Agenda for March 7, 1991, meeting; proposed agenda for annual meeting of May 15, 1991; proposed calendar, 1991-92; State Education Department press releases; newspaper clippings re SUNY officials' pay raises, possible closure of campus, program elimination
- TECB Meeting 12/14/90, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  Agenda for fall meeting, September 24, 1990; membership list; treasurer's report, September 24, 1990; conference agenda; newsletter; State Education Department press releases; Regents action item, A New Compact for Learning, August 30, 1990
- TECB Executive Committee Meeting 3/7/91, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  Agenda
- TECB Meeting-Conference Room B 9/24/90, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  Agenda; membership list; treasurer's report; newsletter; State Education Department press releases; Regents action item, A New Compact for Learning, August 30, 1990; minutes of TECB meeting of May 2, 1990
- TECB Meeting 5/2/90, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  Agenda for TECB Executive Committee, May 2, 1990; proposed agenda for annual meeting; staff consultant's report, 1989-90 (Kiepper), May 1, 1990; budget, 1990-91; treasurer's report, May 2, 1990; proposed calendar, 1990-91; State Education Department Bulletin of Information for Candidates (1990 Series NYS Regents Empire State Challenger Scholarships and Fellowships for Teachers); action item, Strengthening Students' Understanding of One Another, Our Culture, and The World
- TECB Meeting-NYC 2/9/90, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  Agenda; State Education Department (SED)/Regents discussion item, Report on Qualified Staff in New York City; agenda for tech conference and educational software demonstration; SED press releases; newspaper clippings
- TECB Meeting-NYC-12/7/89, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  Minutes of September 22, 1989, meeting; minutes of meetings of December 7 and September 22, 1989; minutes of TECB Executive Committee meeting of October 20, 1989; treasurer's report, December 7, 1989; Educational Testing Service working papers toward a New Generation of Teacher Assessments, September 1989
- TECB Meeting-Conference Room B 9/22/89, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 45)
  Treasurer's report, September 22, 1989; minutes of May 5, 1989, meeting; 1988-89 membership list; list of articles for fall newsletter; spring/summer newsletter; newspaper clipping
- TECB Meeting-NYSUT 5/5/89, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  Agenda for annual meeting; staff consultant report, 1988-89 (Kiepper), May 5, 1989
- Opinion Cartoon, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  Albany Times-Union editorial cartoon re Gov. Hugh Carey and Chancellor Wharton, budget
- TECB Meeting/Position Paper, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  Position paper by Daniel E. Griffiths, NYU and TECB, "Responding to the Crisis in American Education," blaming the women's movement (and attendant abortion, birth control, and divorce) for teacher shortage, student shortage, and decline in societal cohesion, March 9; outline of two other position papers by different authors re staff development and curriculum; minutes of May 4, 1989, meeting; membership list; handwritten notes; newspaper clipping
- TECB Photos, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  Black and white photos of James Kiepper, Hugh Petrie (TECB president), Murray Schneider (NYS Federation of School Administrators) and Domenick R. Uzzi, at meeting
- UUP Photographs, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  Black and white photos of TECB annual meeting and press conference, May 6, 1983
- Photographs TECB Executive Committee, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  9/12/86. Black and white photographs of meeting, including NYSUT vice president Antonia Cortese
- Robert Burnham Photographs and Vita (Box 4, Folder 52)
  Group photo; vita of Robert Burnham, professor of Educational Administration and dean of School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions, New York University
- SUC Buffalo Hearing on Task Force on Teacher Education Certification-Cassette Tape, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  4/25/77 Cassette tape
- Gordon Ambach Photographs (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Professional portrait of Education Commissioner; candid photo at meeting; contact sheet
- TECB Conference Photographs, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  11/16/85. Black and white photos
- Shanker Photographs, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  April. Group photos with UFT president Al Shanker; contact sheets
- TECB Conference Photographs-Hilton Hotel-Albany, NY, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  11/15-16/85. Color snapshots of luncheon audience
- Heidi Mahoney-Assistant Commissioner Post-Secondary Policy Analysis Photographs, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  April. Professional portrait and candids; contact sheet and negatives
- TECB Photographs, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  Black and white group photos; contact sheet and negatives
- TECAP Meeting-Jane Faggen-NTE/ETS Photographs, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  3/23/84. Black and white photos
- Dan Griffiths-Farewell Party, Desmond Americana-Passing of Gavel Photographs, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  June. Black and white photos; contact sheet and negatives
- TECB Photographs, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  Contact sheet and negatives
- TECB Photographs, 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  Photo of fall meeting, September 24, 1982
- Spring Newsletter Photographs, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  Photos; contact sheets
- TECB Meeting Photographs, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  3/8/85. Group photos, some with Al Shanker
- COTE Photographs, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  Photos at 1980 and 1982 meetings; portrait of Regent Floyd S. Linton
- TECB Meeting Photographs 9/25/80, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  Black and white photos
- NYSUT News Release, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  Photographs (crowd shots); NYSUT press release, "NYSUT Teachers Will Conduct Counter Learning Day Salute," May 6, 1980 (counter to NEA salute)
- TECB Meeting Photographs 9/25/80, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Neil Postman-Childhood's End-TCEB Meeting, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Photographs of meeting; contact sheet; photo of Postman; text of "Address to NY Alliance for Public Schools: Workshop for Principals: Childhood's End," Neil Postman, New York University, April 24, 1980
- TECB Meeting Photographs-NYU-3/5/92, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  Photos
- Shirley Brown/Mimi Lieber Vita, 1979-1981 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  Photo portrait, bio, and vita of Mimi Lieber, Regent; vita of Shirley C. Brown, Regent; State Education Department press release, "Chancellor, Commissioner Announce Plans for 1981 Series of Regional Conferences"
- TECB Newsletter, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  Photograph of Regent Emlyn I. Griffith, 1979; list of Regents, with contact information; biographies of Griffith and Regent Robert M. Best; State Education Department press release, "Regents to Conduct April Meeting," April 13, 1982, and newsletter, Inside Education; newspaper clipping re Regent Best; handwritten notes for spring newsletter
- TECB Meeting Photographs (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Black and white photos of meeting
- Teacher Preparation in NYS, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Feb. Document by Office of Higher Education and the Professions
- TECB and Inservice, 1977-1978 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  Summary Report and Recommendations of the 1977 NYS Invitational Conference on Inservice Education, October 20-22, 1977, prepared by the Conference Planning Committee; Definition and Purposes of Inservice Education; Perspectives on Inservice Education, prepared and presented by Confederated Organizations for Teacher Education (COTE), submitted to the Ad Hoc Planning Committee Conference on Inservice in NYS, Summer 1977; memo to TECB, "Some Reflections on Continuing Education and the Control of It," November 3, 1976; Federal Register: Department of Health, Education, and Welfare: Teacher Centers Program Grant Requirements, January 11, 1978; TECB memo re inservice conference, May 2, 1977; related materials
- TECB Annual Meeting Photographs-NYSUT-Albany, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  5/8/91. Negatives
- TECB Meeting Photographs 3/6/81, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  Photos and contact sheet
- TECB Photos (Box 5, Folder 27)
  Color and black and white photos
- TECB Meeting Photographs, 1979 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  9/28/79. Photo and contact sheet
- TECB Meeting Photographs 5/6/88, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  Photos, contact sheet, and negatives
- TECB Photos Misc., 1977 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  Photos, contact sheet; N.Y.S.C.S.S. (NYS Council for Social Studies) newsletter, June (vol. 5, no. 4)
- TECB Meeting Photographs 9/25/87, 1987 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- TECB Membership Lists, 1981-1983 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  Handwritten notes from TECB meeting of March 9, 1984; copy of check to James Kiepper for staff consultant fee, July 10, 1990; TECB membership lists
- NYU Dinner for Dean Griffiths-NYC Club, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  5/19/83. Program; Faculty Council Special Resolution establishing research fund
- TECB Executive Committee-NYSUT Albany, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  1/8/85. Agenda; handwritten notes from meeting; draft document, Rationale for the Summit; newspaper clippings
- TECB Annual Meeting Minutes, 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  Agenda of March 9, 1984, meeting; minutes of December 7, 1984, meeting; Reactions to Preliminary Report on Teaching as a Profession, by Daniel E. Griffiths, president, TECB, September 10, 1979; speech by Vince Gazzetta at COTE spring conference, "Managing the Immediate Details of Certification for Teachers in New York State," with cover letter to TECB from staff consultant James Kiepper, May 16, 1984
- TECB Meeting-NYU-3/5/82, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  Agendas for meetings of March 5 and May 6-7, 1982; handwritten notes; minutes of TECB meeting of January 11, 1982; proposed calendar 1982-83; treasurer's reports, March 5 and May 6, 1982; proposal for TECB position paper, January 21, 1981; drafts of position paper with handwritten notations and separate critique, "Teaching Moral Standards: Establishing a School Climate for Moral Development," Roger V. Burton, SUNY Buffalo, July 1981
- TECB-Treasurer's Reports/Minutes, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  Agenda for October 12, 1984, meeting; minutes of May 4, 1984, meeting; treasurer's report; report of highlights of Regents meeting, September 20-21, 1984; cover letter to TECB members who could not attend the October 12 meeting, with list of materials distributed
- NYS Special Task Force on Equity and Excellence in Education Report, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  Sept. Bound second interim report
- Teaching as a Profession Testimony-Albany, NY, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  4/11/80. Text of testimony by school superintendents, teachers association presidents, PTA, and others to Board of Regents
- TECB and Task Force, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  Program for Teacher Education Conference by New York State Teachers Association (NYSTA) and United Teachers of New York (UTNY), forming New York Congress of Teachers, August 10-11, 1972; correspondence re Teacher Education and Certification Task Force; minutes of September 27, 1974, meeting of TECB
- TECB Minutes and Extra, 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  Agenda of February 17, 1977, meeting; constitution of TECB; minutes of June 19, 1975, meeting; memo from Margaret Lindsey to NYS Task Force on Teacher Education and Certification, expressing concern over the direction of the task force, c. April 1976
- "Teaching as a Profession and Teacher Competence", 1980 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  3/18. State Education Department publication, "Invitation to React to Regents Tentative Proposal on Teaching as a Profession and Teacher Competence," March 7, 1980; NYSUT Comments on the Regents Proposal, March 18, 1980
- TECB Newsletter, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  March. Handwritten and typed articles; layout; background materials; printed spring edition
- Copy Prep. from Roslyn Herman, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  Typed articles
- Reception Dinner/Regrets, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 45)
  Letters of invitation; handwritten notes
- Tom Hobart for Dean Griffiths, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  Testimony of Thomas Y. Hobart, Jr., president, NYSUT, to the Board of Regents on Teaching as a Profession, February 25, 1981; earlier drafts; testimony by NYSUT vice president Antonia Cortese
- Regents Conference-Recruitment and Career Expectations for Teaching, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  11/8/80. Draft conference report, "Recruitment and Career Expectations for Teaching: The Profession in the 80s," November 7, 8, 1980; article on Teaching as a Profession in State Education Department's Inside Education magazine, September/October 1980; copy of Education Times, with cover note; newspaper clippings re resignation of first black female Regent; recommended participants for conference on strengthening recruitment for teaching and allied fields; letter inviting TECB to participate in Regents Conference on Recruitment and Career Expectations; biography of Vivian Anderson, special assistant to executive deputy commissioner of education
- Board of Regents Convocation Reception and Dinner, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  5/23/84. Table Directory, Guests of the University of the State of New York Bicentennial Dinner, May 23, 1984; program, The Ninety-Sixth Convocation of the University of the State of New York: The Bicentennial of the Board of Regents and the University of the State of New York; printed invitations
- Phi Delta Kappa Article, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 49)
  Recommendations of the Commissioner's Task Force on Teacher Education and Certification, April 1, 1977; memo to Regents from Commissioner Nyquist with his recommendations and summary of oral and written comments on the report from hearings, May 25; TECB mailing list; handwritten notes
- Draft Testimony-Dean Griffiths-NYC, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  4/9/80. Drafts of testimony by Daniel Griffiths, president, TECB; testimony on Teaching as a Profession, by Barbara Diebold, vice president, NY Educators Association; testimony of Harvey Inventasch, April 11, 1980; handwritten notes
- Teaching as a Profession Testimony, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  NYSUT Resolution on the Regents Tentative Proposal on Teaching as a Profession and Teacher Competence Introduced as a Special Order of Business by the Board of Directors to the 1980 Representative Assembly; draft testimony by NYSUT president Tom Hobart; NYSUT document, Teaching as a Profession Areas of Focus for Testimony; handwritten notes
- Articles and Clippings, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 52)
  Newspaper clippings on a wide range of education trends
- Articles and Clippings, 1980-1982 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- TECB Position Paper-Morality in the Classroom, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  Drafts of paper; cover letter from author Roger V. Burton, professor at SUNY Buffalo, to TECB staff consultant James Kiepper; critique of paper by Robert H. Koff, dean at SUNY Albany; critique of paper by James F. Collins, director of Syracuse University School of Education; handwritten notes; minutes of TECB meeting of September 24, 1982, with consideration of position paper as agenda item
- Teaching as a Profession Legislation-Entrance Exam Announcement, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Folder 55)